Some debts can't be paid.
Inherit the Viper is a crime, thriller, drama film directed by Anthony Jerjen.
Since the death of their father, the Riley siblings have kept their
heads above water by illegally dealing in painkillers.
Josie is managing the business with an iron fist, when her brother, War veteran Kip, is concerned that
the risky business is increasingly turning them into outsiders in their small community.
While Kip wants to keep his younger brother out of their illegal
endeavors, his younger brother is already making plans of his own.
Kip Conley, played by Josh Hartnett.
Josie Conley, played by Margarita Levieva.
Boots Conley, played by Owen Teague.
Eve, played by Valorie Curry.
Clay Carter, played by Bruce Dern.
Cooper, played by Chandler Riggs.
Inherit the Viper is a 2019 American crime drama film directed by Anthony Jerjen, in
his feature directorial debut, from a screenplay by Andrew Crabtree.
It stars Josh Hartnett, Margarita Levieva, Chandler Riggs, Bruce
Dern, Valorie Curry, Owen Teague and Dash Mihok.
Inherit the Viper had its world premiere at the 2019 Zurich Film Festival, and was released in a limited
theatrical engagement before premiering on video-on-demand on January 10, 2020, by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of small town, ohio, industry, drug dealing, drugs.
The tone is emotional and intense.